

Manuel Duran

Career Summary

Computer Engineer, 3 years of experience in application development focused on the frontend area oriented to web development. Experience with React, Express, NodeJS and Mongo under the framework of agile methodologies and deployment of modern applications with GCP and Netlify.

Summary of Qualifications

Proficient In:

HTML

React

Mongo

Google Cloud

CSS

Material UI

PostgreSQLApollo Graph

Netlify

JavaScript

Gastby

Sastby •

Languages

Spanish (native speaker)

English (advanced)

Career History

GLOBANT, Santiago, Chile

Web Developer UI

Feb. 2022 – Nowadays

Jun. 2021 – Feb. 2022

AMICAR, Santiago, Chile

Frontend Developer

- Retake and launching to production the project "Amices", focusing on vehicle credit simulations, store client data and connection with different financial entities,
- Maintain not only the frontend of the project but also make modifications in the queries generated to the core from the backend to the core using mongoose DB and Sequelize from the core to the database in Postgres.
- Understand and maintain major changes and modifications at the core of the business.

BACO Restaurant, Santiago, Chile

Feb. 2020 – May. 2021

Web Developer

- Develop a food delivery application with a Backoffice, API connection and sales registration for service, delivery control and control of online orders through a webapp for the company.
- Development of a dynamic responsive web digital food menu based on the QR model for the different branches of the company.
- Updating and modernization of the website and different digital channels of the company

SMARTBOT, Santiago, Chile

Feb. 2017 - Feb. 2020

Tecnical Developer

- Assembly and commissioning of solutions in applied robotics services.
- Programmer, designer and maintenance of security robotics equipment and user service.

Education

territorial polytechnic university of Aragua, La Victoria, Venezuela

Jan. 2009 – Jun. 2014

Computer Engineer